(理央)これは
思春期症候群ではなく
To be clear, we're talking established quantum mechanics here, not Puberty Syndrome.
あくまで量子力学の世界における
解釈だよ｡
この中に 猫と 更に
You put a cat in a box,
along with a substance which emits radiation once per hour
１時間に１度の確率で
放射線を発する放射性原子と
その放射線を感知して
毒ｶﾞｽを発生する装置を
and a device which emits a poisonous gas
upon detecting that radiation.
一緒に入れておく｡
Then you close the box and wait thirty minutes.
これでﾌﾀをして 30分待つ｡
Okay, here's a box I prepared thirty minutes earlier.
さて ここに30分待った
箱を用意した｡
What's this, a cooking show?
(咲太)料理番組か｡
箱の中の猫は
What do you think happened to the cat in the box?
どうなってると思う？
生きているか 死んでいるか｡
Is it alive or dead?
１時間に１回の確率で
毒ｶﾞｽが出るわけだから
If the poisonous gas is released once per hour,
then after half an hour, it's a fifty-fifty chance, right?
30分だと 五分五分だろ？
The only way you can determine the cat's
present state is by checking.
今の状態を確定するためには
見るしかない｡
In other words, until you open the box and see,
the cat is both half alive and half dead.
つまり ﾌﾀを開けて
確認するまで
猫は 半分生きていて
半分死んでいることになる｡
人間も同じってことか？
And you mean to say people are the same?
観測者によって確認されるまで
存在は確定しない…｡
One's existence isn't confirmed
until they're seen by an observer?
May 20th
Episode 2: First Dates Are Always Chaotic
この絵ﾂﾞﾗは 完璧にｶｯﾌﾟﾙだよな｡
Man, we totally look like a couple.
(麻衣)何か言った？
いえ 何も｡
Did you say something?
No, nothing.
大丈夫よ どうせ 私の姿は
周りには見えてないから｡
Don't worry. No one else can see me anyway.
How does that carrot you're holding look to people who can't see you?
今 麻衣さんが握っているﾆﾝｼﾞﾝは
麻衣さんが見えてない人には
どう見えてるんですか？
見えてないみたいよ｡
It turns invisible too, apparently.
ほらね｡
See?
たぶん 私が触れたものは
見えなくなるのよ｡
Anything I touch probably turns invisible to them.
じゃあ 僕が麻衣さんに触れたら
どうなるのかな？
What if I touched you, then?
Are you hinting that you want to hold hands with me?
それは 私と手をつなぎたい
っていうｱﾋﾟｰﾙ？
いや あくまで実験｡
No, I mean as an experiment.
そんな理由なら
つないであげない｡
That's not a good enough reason for me.
あ… ﾎﾝﾄは 麻衣さんと
手をつなぎたいだけです｡
Actually, I just want to hold hands with you.
それで？
And?
女子と 手すらつないだことのない
僕の初めてを
I've never held hands with a girl before.
Please take my first time.
もらってください｡
若干気持ち悪いけど…｡
That was a bit gross,
but I'll give you a pass.
まっ 合格にしてあげる｡
You're thinking dirty thoughts right now, aren't you?
今 ｴﾛいこと考えてるでしょ？
麻衣さんの想像の100倍は
ｴﾛいこと考えてる｡
Yeah. A hundred times dirtier than what you're imagining.
でも 大人の麻衣さんは
それくらい平気だよね｡
But a mature lady such as yourself wouldn't be rattled by that, right?
Right.
そうね 年下の男の子に
ｴｯﾁな妄想をされるくらい
A younger boy having sexual fantasies about me
なんでもない｡
ｳﾊｯ！
doesn't bother me at all!
僕のことは見えてるみたい｡
Looks like they can still see me.
麻衣さんの家 楽しみだなぁ｡
I can't wait to see your place, Mai-san.
I'm not letting you in. I live alone.
入れないわよ 一人暮らしだし｡
え～｡
だいたい私たち
What?
Besides, we haven't made up yet, have we?
まだｹﾝｶ中でしょ｡
あれは麻衣さんが
That's because you won't be honest with yourself.
素直じゃないから｡ 演技の仕事
したいなら続ければいいのに｡
If you want to keep acting, what's stopping you?
余計な口をはさまないで｡
I didn't ask for your opinion.
You don't know anything.
何も知らないくせに｡
知ってますよ｡
Oh, I do.
中３のときに出した
写真集が原因なんですよね｡
Your photo collection from three years ago was the cause, right?
水着は絶対NGって
条件だったのに
You'd refused to pose in swimsuits,
ﾏﾈｰｼﾞｬｰだった お母さんが
勝手に契約しちゃったとか｡
but your manager—your mom—
agreed to it in the contract anyway.
それで大ｹﾞﾝｶになって
芸能活動休止って やり方で
That caused a huge rift between you two,
and you went on hiatus
お母さんに仕返しをした｡
to get one up over your mom.
けど そんなのふざけてる｡
うるさい｡
But that's completely messed up.
Shut up.
What's the point if you have to
throw away your dreams too?
一緒に自分の欲しいものまで
投げ捨てたんじゃ意味ないし｡
Shut up already!
うるさいな！ 私だって
いっぱい悩んで決めたの｡
You have no idea how hard a decision it was!
まだ中学生だったのよ｡
なのに ｽﾀｼﾞｵに入ったら
I was still in middle school, you know?
But I got to the studio
and saw a swimsuit ready for me.
水着がいきなり用意されてて
もう契約したからって言われて
やるしかなくて…｡
They said I'd agreed to it in the contract,
so I had to do it.
むりやり
笑顔をつくるしかなかった｡
I had to force a smile while dying inside!
結局 あの人は 私を使って
お金儲けすることしか
I realized she never cared about anything other than making money off of me!
考えてなかったのよ｡
だったら なおさら
芸能界に戻るべきだと思う｡
That's all the more reason
for you to go back to work.
どうしてよ？
麻衣さんが いまだに
Why?
To cleanse the bad taste it's left in your mouth.
嫌な思いをしているから｡
やりたいなら 我慢なんて
しなければいい｡
If you want to do it, don't hold back.
やればいい 麻衣さんだって
本当は わかってるはずだ｡
Just do it.
Deep down, you should know this yourself.
Who was it that told you why I went on hiatus?
活動休止の理由 誰に聞いたの？
え？
目をそらすな｡
Don't look away!
Ow!
ｲﾀﾀ… かえで事件のとき
I've known this news anchor since she came
to see Kaede for a story on bullying back then.
いじめの取材で来た
ｱﾅｳﾝｻｰの知り合いがいて
南条文香っていう｡
ああ あの人｡
Her name's Nanjou Fumika.
Oh, her? I've worked with her too.
私も お世話になったことある｡
あの人 思春期症候群に
興味を持って
She's taken an interest in Puberty Syndrome
and is researching the topic.
調べているんですよ｡
咲太くん
Sakuta-kun, did you have to give something up
in exchange for information about me?
私の情報を得るために
何か取り引きをしたってこと？
写真を… 胸の傷を１枚｡
A photo.
I let her take one of my scars.
ﾊﾞｶ！ 家まで取材のｶﾒﾗが来るわよ｡
You idiot! You'll have reporters and cameramen hounding you at home!
待ち伏せされて 囲まれて
They'll ambush and surround you,
妹さんも嫌な思いを
するかもしれないのよ｡
and probably your sister, too!
あの女の連絡先をよこしなさい｡
麻衣さん 女王様すぎ｡
Give me that woman's number. Now.
You're way too bossy.
And you're not taking TV seriously enough.
咲太くんはﾃﾚﾋﾞなめすぎ｡
突然 失礼します｡
I'm sorry for calling so abruptly.
I'm Sakurajima Mai. We've worked together before.
以前 お世話になったことのある
桜島麻衣と申します｡
ご無沙汰しています｡
今 お時間よろしいでしょうか？
It's been far too long.
Do you have time now?
(南条)咲太くんの件？
２人は どういうご関係？
You want to talk about Sakuta-kun?
How do you two know each other?
[℡]彼 高校の後輩なんです｡
He's my junior in school.
[℡]彼の胸の傷の写真
I'd like you to refrain from showing the photo of his scars on TV.
ﾃﾚﾋﾞに出すのを
やめていただきたいんです｡
代わりに あるｽｸｰﾌﾟを
私が提供します｡
In return, I'll give you a big scoop.
ちょ ちょっと麻衣さん｡
ｼｯ！
H-Hey, Mai-san!
Shh.
近々 私は芸能活動を再開します｡
I'm going to return to showbiz soon.
母の事務所には戻りません｡
I won't be rejoining my mother's agency.
復帰は別の事務所からになります｡
I'll be returning under a different label.
その際は 御社と南条さんの
独占取材を確約します｡
I promise you exclusive access when that happens.
すみません…｡
なんで謝るのよ｡
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
でも 芸能界復帰って…｡
Because I made you go back to showbiz.
咲太くんの
言ったとおりだと思ったのよ｡
I simply realized you were right.
ﾄﾞﾗﾏや映画の仕事は好きだったし
ずっと続けたいと思ってた｡
I liked working on TV shows and movies,
and I always wanted to make that my career.
その気持ちに
ｳｿをつき続けてたから
I'd been lying to myself about that,
思春期症候群なんて
おかしなことに
and maybe that's why I ended up with this crazy Puberty Syndrome or whatever.
なってるのかもって｡
だから 今夜は
I came to see you tonight to let you know.
それを伝えるために来たの｡
And also because I was hungry, of course.
もちろん お腹が空いてたってのも
あるけど｡
We're here. This is where I live.
ここよ 私の家｡
えっ!? うちの
すぐそばじゃないですか｡
Huh?
You live right across the street from me?
さっきは叩いてごめん
荷物ありがと｡
Sorry for slapping you earlier,
and thanks for carrying my stuff.
Oh, right. Make time on Sunday.
You're coming with me.
そうだ 日曜日 つきあいなさい｡
芸能界復帰したら
遊んでる余裕もないだろうから｡
Once I go back to work,
I won't have time to go out and have fun.
こっちに２年住んでるのに
私 鎌倉にも行ってないの｡
Did you know I've lived here for two years
and I haven't even been to Kamakura?
それって…｡
ﾃﾞｰﾄじゃないから｡
You mean...
It's not a date.
え…｡
じゃ ２時半に
Okay, see you in front of the Enoden
Fujisawa Station ticket gates at 2:30 PM.
江ノ電 藤沢駅の改札前｡
１秒でも遅れたら帰るから｡
I'll leave if you're even a second late, okay?
《結局 僕が何をしようが
関係なく
Ultimately, it didn't matter what I did.
麻衣さんは全部
自分で決めたってことか》
Mai-san decided everything herself.
And the world keeps going 'round, huh?
世界なんて
勝手に回ってんだなぁ｡
ひゃっほう！
Yahoo!
What's the matter, Onii-chan?!
(かえで)お兄ちゃん
どうしました!?
こら 覗くんじゃない｡
Hey, don't peek.
Let me share in your "yahoo" too!
お兄ちゃんの ひゃっほう！ を
かえでにも分けてください｡
May 25Th
May 25th
男は あらゆる事態に
備えておくべきなんだ｡
Guys gotta be ready for everything.
どうした？
What's wrong?
うわ～ ﾏﾏじゃない｡
You're not Mommy!
A lost kid, huh?
迷子か｡
お兄ちゃんがﾏﾏを捜してやるから
もう泣くな｡
Don't cry. I'll look for your mommy.
ﾎﾝﾄ？
ああ｡
Really?
Really.
Die, pedo scum!
くたばれ ﾛﾘｺﾝ変質者！
うっ…｡
今のうちに逃げて！
Run away!
ちょっと待て！
誰がﾛﾘｺﾝ変質者だ｡
Hold it!
Who're you calling a pedo?!
さぁ 早く！
だから 違うって｡
Now!
You've got it all wrong!
That girl's lost! I was just trying to help look for her mother!
その子は迷子｡ 僕は一緒に
母親を捜そうとしてただけだ｡
Huh?
Yeah.
Ah...
あ…｡
あ～ 痛い｡
Man, that hurts.
S-Sorry.
ごめんね ｱﾊﾊ…｡
２つにﾊﾟｯｸﾘ割れたかも｡
I think my butt split into two.
What? That's bad!
えっ ﾔﾊﾞｯ！ って
元から２つじゃん｡
Wait, they're always like that!
もう わかった わかりました｡
Jeez, fine! I get it!
Do it!
Huh?
Kick me! And then we'll be even!
いいから蹴って
これで おあいこでしょ｡
Uh, even?
いや おあいこって…｡
Hurry up! I'm supposed to be meeting a friend!
早く！ 私
友達との約束があるの｡
約束なら 僕だって…｡
だったら早く！
I'm supposed to be meeting someone too.
Then get a move on!
あ～ もう わかったよ｡
Okay, fine.
えいっ！
痛か～！
Damn, that hurts!
あ～ ちょっと君 何やってんの？
You there. What do you think you're doing?
Jeez, what a disaster.
は～ もう最悪｡
それは こっちのｾﾘﾌだ｡
Took the words right out of my mouth.
お前が ｽﾏﾎばかり気にしてるから
お説教が長引いたんだろ｡
We'd have been out faster if you
hadn't been fiddling with your phone.
だって ﾒｯｾｰｼﾞ来てたし
But I'd gotten all these messages.
返事早くしないと
友達じゃなくなっちゃう｡
If I didn't reply quickly, they'd stop being my friends.
はぁ…｡
あっ そうだ 私 約束が…｡
Oh, right! I'm meeting someone!
ﾔﾊﾞｯ 遅刻だ！ じゃあな｡
Crap, I'm late!
See you!
Of course she left.
まっ そりゃそうだよな｡
You've got some nerve, making me wait
one hour and thirty-eight minutes.
私を１時間38分も待たせるなんて
いい身分ね｡
なによ｡
麻衣さんは
What?
Mai-san's not the kind of nice girl
who'd wait for a guy who was late.
遅刻してきた男を
けなげに待っているような
かわいげのある女じゃない｡
さては偽者だな！
You must be an impostor!
咲太が 私を
どういう目で見ているのか
I now understand very well how you see me, Sakuta.
よくわかったわ｡
｢くん｣が抜けてますよ｡
You're forgetting something.
咲太なんて 咲太で十分｡
"Sakuta" is all you deserve to be called.
遅刻の理由はわかったけど
本当にそれだけ？
I get why you were late, but was that really all?
That was all.
それだけです｡
もし ｳｿだったら
If I find out you're lying,
I'll make you eat Pocky through your nose.
鼻でﾎﾟｯｷｰ食べてもらうから｡
１本？
１箱｡
One?
One box.
Say, why do you even care about me?
ねぇ 咲太は どうして
私にかまうの？
え？
普通は 私みたいに
Normally, one would stay away from a troublesome girl like me.
面倒な女には関わらない｡
I bet it's because of that cynical outlook that you can't make any friends.
そんなふうに ひねくれてるから
友達できないんですよ
麻衣さんは｡
まじめに答えなさい｡
Give me a straight answer.
私に お節介を焼くのはどうして？
Why do you go out of your way to help me?
美人の先輩と お近づきになれる
ﾁｬﾝｽだから
I'm all fired up because this is my chance to get close to a hot older girl.
張り切っているんです｡
誰が 本音を
Who asked you to reveal your ulterior motive?
赤裸々に語れと言ったのよ｡
まじめにって言ったの
You're the one who asked for a straight answer.
麻衣さんだよね｡
困ってるのに 誰にも頼れないのは
しんどいからですよ｡
Because it sucks to not have anybody to lean on when you're in trouble.
When Kaede developed her Puberty Syndrome,
nobody believed us.
妹のかえでが
思春期症候群になったとき
誰も信じてくれなくて…｡
ご両親は？
What about your parents?
We're living separately now.
Mom couldn't accept what happened to Kaede.
今は 別々に暮らしてます｡
母さんは かえでに起きたことを
受け止め切れなくて…｡
But there was just one person who heard me out.
でも １人だけいたんですよ｡
まじめに聞いてくれた人が｡
その人と会ってなければ
僕は乗り切れなかったと思う｡
If I hadn't met them, I don't think I could've gotten through it.
だから 僕も麻衣さんにとって
その人のようになれたらって…｡
So I want to be there for you
like they were for me.
それ 女でしょ｡
え？
It was a girl, wasn't it?
降りる｡
え？ 鎌倉は？
I'm getting off.
Huh? What about Kamakura?
咲太が遅刻したせいで
もう夕方だし｡
Forget it. You were so late
the sun's already going down.
あっ 待って｡
H-Hey, wait!
Teenage Pig Doesn't
Dream of Bunny Girls
⦅知ってますか？
Did you know?
人の目の高さから見える
水平線までの距離は
The distance from your eye level to the horizon
約４kmなんですよ｡
is around four kilometers.
私は 牧之原翔子です｡
I'm Makinohara Shouko.
牧之原ｻｰﾋﾞｽｴﾘｱの牧之原に
大空を翔る子の翔子｡
Shouko with the character for flying, like in the sky,
and Makinohara from "Makinohara Service Area."
少年の名前は？⦆
What's your name?
出会ったのは 僕が中３
彼女は高２｡
I was in the second year of middle school,
and she was two years above me.
峰ヶ原高校の制服を着ていました｡
She was wearing Minegahara High's uniform.
もしかして その人を追いかけて
峰ヶ原高校を受験したわけ？
Wait, did you apply to
Minegahara High because of her?
まぁ そのとおりです｡
でも ふられちゃったんだ？
Well, yeah.
But she turned you down, huh?
No, I didn't ask her out.
いえ 告白はしてません｡
会えなかったんで｡
I never even saw her.
峰ヶ原高校に そんな生徒は
存在してなかったんです｡
There was no such student in Minegahara High.
在校生の名簿も全部調べたけど
いなかった｡
I went through the whole student roster,
but I couldn't find her.
でも 僕は確かに
牧之原翔子って人と出会って
But I definitely did meet a girl called Makinohara Shouko,
その人の存在に救われたんです｡
and she certainly did
get me back on my feet.
今でも彼女のことが好き？
Do you still like her?
すげえ好きでした｡
I liked her a lot.
I can't believe you're talking about how you like another girl while on a date.
ﾃﾞｰﾄの最中に
他の女が好きだなんて 最低｡
自分から聞いておいて？
But you were the one who asked.
And I said I liked her, past tense!
That's an important difference!
あと ｢好きだった｣だから｡
そこ重要｡
来たみたい｡
There she is.
誰ですか？
Who's that?
Sent Messages
To:
Manager
(no subject)
Come to Shichirigahama Beach
at 5 PM on Sunday 25th
ﾏﾈｰｼﾞｬｰって…
麻衣さんのお母さん!?
"Manager"?
Wait, your mother?!
芸能界復帰の話
I need to tell her I'm going back to showbiz,
他の事務所との契約のこと
ちゃんと話しておかないとね｡
and that I'm signing with another agency.
Will you be okay?
大丈夫なんですか？
終わったら
ﾃﾞｰﾄの続きしてあげるから
We can continue our date
once I'm done, so wait for me.
待ってなさい｡
ｳｿだろ…｡
Are you kidding me?
あなたなの？ 私を
こんなところに呼び出したのは｡
Were you the one who called me out here?
Who are you? What do you want?
誰？ 何の用？
梓川咲太といいます｡
I'm Azusagawa Sakuta. Mai-san's junior.
麻衣さんの後輩です｡
誰の後輩？
Whose junior?
Mai-san's.
麻衣さんです｡
誰よ それ｡
Who is that?
What do you mean, "who"? Your daughter!
誰って… あんたの娘でしょ！
何言ってるの
私に娘なんていないわ｡
What are you talking about?
I don't have a daughter.
冗談はよして｡
冗談はどっちだ！
Quit messing around.
Right back at you!
ﾒｰﾙ… 今日 ここで会う約束を｡
これでしょ？
What about the text?
The one that brought you here.
You mean this?
でも 差出人が不明なの｡
Mai
Sender:
(no subject)
Come to Shichirigahama Beach
at 5 PM on Sunday 25th
Sender:
(no subject)
Come to Shichirigahama Beach
at 5 PM on Sunday 25th
Sender:
(no subject)
Come to Shichirigahama Beach
at 5 PM on Sunday 25th
The sender's name is blanked out.
Sender
無理に時間をあけて
予定入れたのは
I remember rearranging my schedule
to make it here, but...
覚えているんだけど…
何なのかしら これ｡
What's all this about?
This can't be happening!
そんなﾊﾞｶなことがあるか！
母親なのに なんで
娘を忘れられるんだ！
You're her mother! How could you forget your own daughter?!
That's enough.
もういい！
なんで？
Why? I'm not done with her!
まだ話は終わってない｡
お願い もうやめて｡
Please, just drop it.
Enough with your pranks.
変ないたずらは やめなさい｡
これ以上は
つきあってられないわ｡
I can't deal with this anymore.
Hey, excuse me.
あの すみません｡
Do you remember Sakurajima Mai?
桜島麻衣をご存じですか？
ほら 朝ﾄﾞﾗでﾌﾞﾚｰｸした…｡
Y'know, the girl who got her big break in a morning soap.
う～ん 知らないねぇ｡
No, can't say I do.
《見えなくなるということは
ただ見えないだけじゃなくて
What if becoming invisible to people didn't just mean they couldn't see you anymore?
記憶からも
消えてしまうことだとしたら…》
What if you disappeared from their memories, too?
Sakurajima Mai? Who's that?
桜島麻衣… 誰 それ？
[℡](南条)もしもし？
Hello?
You don't know Sakurajima Mai?
桜島麻衣を知らないんですか？
[℡]知らないわ｡ 誰よ？
No, I don't. Who's that?
じゃあ 写真の件は？
What about the photo, then?
You mean the deal where I promised not to show it? Don't worry, I remember.
あれは出さないって約束でしょ｡
覚えてるわよ｡
And who'd you make that deal with?
[℡]約束って 誰と？
With you, obviously.
咲太くんとに決まってるじゃない｡
今日はありがとう｡ じゃ｡
Thanks for today.
See you.
待った！
Wait!
麻衣さん 行こう！
行くって どこへ？
Let's go, Mai-san!
Go where?
どこか遠くの街へ行けば
If we go to some faraway town,
we might find people who can still see you!
まだ麻衣さんのことを
見れる人がいるかもしれない｡
確かめに行こう｡
Let's go make sure!
確かめてどうするの？
We'll make sure, and then what?
咲太以外には見えなくて
忘れられてることがわかって
How will it help to find out that nobody but you can see or remember me?
何になるのよ！
If nothing else, I can stay by your side that entire time.
少なくとも その間
ずっと僕が そばにいられる｡
For a younger boy, you sure are cheeky.
年下のくせに生意気｡
せっかくのﾃﾞｰﾄだし｡
I just don't want our date to end.
いいわよ まだ私を
帰したくないっていうなら
Very well.
If you're not ready to let me go yet,
ﾃﾞｰﾄの続き してあげる｡
I don't mind continuing our date.
[ﾃｰﾌ]発信音のあとに
ﾒｯｾｰｼﾞをどうぞ｡
Please leave a message after the beep.
Payphone
[℡]かえで 僕だ｡
Kaede, it's me.
もしもし どうしたんですか？
Hello? What's the matter?
[℡]悪い 今日 帰れない｡
Sorry, I won't be home tonight.
[℡]遠くまで行く用事ができた｡
There's somewhere I need to travel.
What for?
(かえで)何ですか？ 用事って｡
Do you remember Sakurajima Mai,
the girl at our place the other day?
[℡]前 うちに来た
桜島麻衣って お姉さんのこと
覚えてるか？
知りませんけど…｡
No, why?
[℡]知らないなら いいんだ｡
今日の夕飯は
Never mind if you don't.
Make do with the cup noodles in the kitchen cupboard for dinner.
ｷｯﾁﾝの戸棚にある
ｶｯﾌﾟ麺で我慢してくれ｡
SPECIAL RAPID SERVICE
[℡]また電話する｡
I'll call again later.
Apparently, it's the second-most populous city in Gifu Prefecture, after Gifu City.
岐阜県の中では 岐阜市に次いで
人口が多いんだって｡
何の話？
大垣｡
What are you talking about?
Ogaki, this train's destination.
この列車の行き先｡
ああ｡
あと 地下水が豊富だって
書いてある｡
Also, it says here that it has a lot of groundwater.
水のきれいなところは大歓迎｡
Nothing beats a place with clean water.
ねぇ 咲太｡
何ですか？
Hey, Sakuta.
What?
私のこと 見えてる？
見えてますよ｡
Can you see me?
Yeah, I see you.
Can you hear my voice?
声 聞こえてる？
ﾊﾞｯﾁﾘと｡
Loud and clear.
私のこと 覚えてる？
桜島麻衣｡
Do you remember me?
Sakurajima Mai.
A third-year at Kanagawa Prefectural Minegahara High School.
神奈川県立峰ヶ原高校３年生｡
子役として芸能界ﾃﾞﾋﾞｭｰして
いろいろと大活躍｡
Made her showbiz debut as a child actress
and spent a lot of time in the spotlight.
性格は歪んでいて 素直じゃない｡
A somewhat twisted character
who has trouble expressing herself.
どこがよ？
不安なくせに
How so?
Like how you're desperately trying to hide how worried you are.
それを隠しているところ｡
私 握っていいなんて言ってない｡
I never said you could hold my hand.
僕は握りたい｡
But I want to.
Oh, fine. Just this one time.
しかたないわね 今だけ特別よ｡
あの 桜島麻衣をご存じですか？
Do you remember Sakurajima Mai?
She was in a shinkansen commercial, too.
新幹線のCMにも出たことのある｡
桜島…｡
Sakurajima? Was there an actress with that name?
そんなﾀﾚﾝﾄいたっけ？
どうも｡
Thank you.
Talk about cramped.
狭っ｡
こんなもんでしょ｡
What did you expect?
お風呂入る｡
えっ!?
I'm taking a shower.
覗かないでよ｡
You'd better not peep.
Don't worry. I can go a whole day
just on the sound of the shower.
大丈夫です 僕は ｼｬﾜｰの音だけで
ご飯３杯は いけるんで｡
ここは音だけ聞かせて
年下の男子をもだえさせるのが
Wouldn't a mature lady actually want to leave me
writhing by letting me hear the sound?
余裕のある大人の女性の
たしなみだと思うけどなぁ｡
わかってるわよ もちろん｡
I know that, obviously!
But don't you dare start doing anything weird by yourself!
その代わり １人で変なこと
始めないでよ｡
変なこと？
"Anything weird"?
ﾊﾞｶ 知らない！
Jerk! Do whatever, see if I care!
今の すげえかわいかったな｡
That was super adorable.
[℡](国見)はい？
あ 国見？ 僕だけど｡
Hello?
Oh, Kunimi? It's me.
[℡]何時だと思ってんだよ｡
What time do you think it is?
1:16 AM.
１時16分だな｡
[℡]わかってるよ そんなこと｡
I know, dumbass.
I need your help. It's serious.
緊急事態なんだ 助けてくれ｡
[℡]何すりゃいいの？
What do you need me to do?
[℡]桜島先輩のこと覚えてるか？
Do you remember Sakurajima-senpai?
は？ 当たり前だろ｡
Huh? Obviously.
Right. Of course you wouldn't—
だよな 知らないよ…
覚えてるのか!?
Wait, you remember who she is?
Sakurajima-senpai?
桜島先輩だぞ？
[℡]だから
Of course I know who she is.
わかるに決まってるだろ｡
用事はそんだけ？
Is that all? I'm going to sleep.
[℡]寝るぞ 俺｡
待った！
Wait. Gimme Futaba's mobile number.
双葉のｹｰﾀｲ番号を教えてくれ｡
何時だと思ってるわけ？
What time do you think it is?
1:19 AM.
１時19分だ｡
[℡](理央)21分｡
It's 1:21. Your clock's behind.
[℡]その時計 遅れてるよ｡
[℡]なるほどね この前の
思春期症候群の話は
I see.
So that's what the Puberty Syndrome talk the other day was about.
そういうことだったのか｡
なんで こんなことが
I need you to figure out why this is happening and how to solve it.
起きているのか
解決する手段を見つけてほしい｡
[℡]むちゃくちゃだね 梓川は｡
必死だからな｡
Do you realize how absurd you're being?
I'm desperate.
前に 国見が言っていたよ｡
Kunimi once told me
that the great thing about you is that you know how to say "thanks," "sorry," and "help me."
｢ありがとう｣と ｢ごめん｣と
｢助けてくれ｣を言えるのが
梓川のいいとこだって｡
明日 学校は？
Coming to school tomorrow?
Probably not in the morning. Why?
朝からは無理だろうな なんで？
[℡]学校に原因が
あるのかもしれないと思った｡
I just thought the cause might lie there.
[℡]桜島先輩のこと
The other students could see Sakurajima-senpai, after all.
学校の生徒たちには
見えていたからね｡
そっか…｡
[℡]もう少し考えてみるけど
I see.
I'll think about it some more, but don't get your hopes up.
期待はしないで｡
ありがと｡
Thank you.
I'll see you at school tomorrow,
though I might only get there by afternoon.
明日は昼になるかもしれないけど
学校には行く｡
夜中に悪かった｡
Sorry to disturb you so late.
Damn, she's done with the shower already!
うわぁ ｼｬﾜｰ終わってる！
What do I do about underwear?
下着 どうしよう｡
は？
I don't mind wearing the same clothes, but not the underwear.
服は一緒でもいいけど 下着は嫌｡
It's a strange feeling.
なんか不思議｡
ん？
こんなふうに
知らない街にいること｡
Being in an unfamiliar town like this.
Haven't you been to all kinds of places for work?
仕事で いろんな場所に
行ったことあるんじゃ？
それは連れていかれてるだけよ｡
あ～ それ わかるなぁ｡
That was just me being taken there by others.
Oh, I get what you mean.
But the strangest feeling is that it's a younger boy walking by my side.
でも いちばん不思議なのは
一緒に歩くのが
年下の男の子ってことね｡
僕だって あの桜島麻衣と
こんな遠い街に来るとは
I never thought I'd come to a faraway town with "the" Sakurajima Mai, either.
思ってませんでした｡
光栄でしょ？
I hope you feel honored.
一生 忘れません｡
I'll remember this for the rest of my life.
絶対 忘れない｡
I'll never forget it.
もし 忘れたら？
And what if you do?
鼻からﾎﾟｯｷｰ食べる｡
I'll eat Pocky through my nose.
狭い｡
僕に出ていけと？
This is cramped.
What, you want me to get out?
何か話して 楽しい話｡
Talk about something fun.
ﾊｰﾄﾞﾙ高いなぁ
僕を困らせて楽しいですか？
You're asking a lot of me here.
Are you having fun putting me on the spot?
咲太だって 私にいじめられて
楽しんでるじゃない｡
Hey, you enjoy having me mess with you too.
こんな美人の先輩に
いじめられて
There isn't a guy out there who wouldn't enjoy being bullied by such a hot older girl.
喜ばない男はいないと思うけどな｡
Is that a compliment?
それ 褒めてるの？
ﾍﾞﾀ褒めです｡
A shower of praise.
ふ～ん｡
Huh...
ねぇ ｷｽしようか｡
Hey, want to kiss?
麻衣さん 欲求不満？
Mai-san, are you feeling sexually frustrated?
ﾊﾞｰｶ もう寝よ おやすみ｡
Dumbass.
Let's just sleep. Good night.
ねぇ 咲太｡
寝るんじゃないんですか？
Hey, Sakuta.
What happened to sleeping?
今 私が 震えながら
消えたくないって言って
What will you do if I start shaking and crying,
saying I don't want to fade away?
泣き出したら どうする？
背中から抱きしめて
Maybe I'll hug you from behind
and whisper into your ear that it'll be all right.
大丈夫だよって
耳元で ささやこうかな｡
じゃあ 絶対に言わない｡
あれ ご不満？
I'm definitely not saying it, then.
Huh? Not happy with that?
どさくさにまぎれて
胸とか触られそうだし｡
I mean, you'll probably take the chance to feel me up.
芸能界への復帰も決めたのに
消えてる場合じゃないのよ｡
Anyway, I've decided to go back to showbiz.
This is no time to be disappearing.
そうですね｡
ﾄﾞﾗﾏに出て 映画も またやりたい｡
Right.
I want to be in TV shows and movies again.
And theater plays too.
舞台のお芝居も｡
せっかく 年下の生意気な男の子と
知り合って
And now that I've come to know a cheeky younger boy,
学校に行くのも
楽しくなってきたのに｡
I've finally started looking forward to school.
I'll never forget you.
僕は絶対に忘れない｡
絶対なんてあるの？
だから
Can you ever say never?
So we can kiss anytime.
It doesn't even have to be me.
ｷｽなんて いつだってできますよ｡
相手が僕じゃなくても｡
I'm sure you can do anything you want with ease.
麻衣さんなら
何だって余裕だと思う｡
何だってできる｡
そうね さっきのが
I suppose.
That was your one and only chance to take my first kiss.
咲太が 私のﾌｧｰｽﾄｷｽを奪える
最初で最後のﾁｬﾝｽだったのに｡
それ 先に言ってくれたら
したのに｡
You know, I would've done it
if you'd mentioned that at the time.
ﾌﾌ… もうﾀﾞﾒ｡
It's too late now.
ありがと｡
Thank you.
私を諦めないでいてくれて
Thank you for not giving up on me.
That's my Sakuta.
Next Episode
#3 A World without You Alone
A total pig.